

# ARITRA GHOSH

**3D ARTIST** 

(Self-taught 3D enthusiast)

#### **About Me**

As a 3D artist, I am passionate about bringing imagination to life through digital art. With a keen eye for detail and a strong technical skillset, I specialize in creating visually stunning 3D models, environments, and animations that capture the essence of the project I'm working on.

#### Personal Details

Date of Birth 21-02-2002

Emailarimanav007@gmail.com

Phone.no 8777694465

#### Website & Social Links

Behance https://www.behance.net/ arizzportfolio

Artstation https://www.artstation.co m/aritraghosh

#### **Software Proficiencies**

Blender 3D 3Dsmax Zbrush

Unreal Engine 5 Unity Game Engine

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Premiere pro

Substance Painter Substance Designer

## Experience

Salvation Games (Sept 2020-Nov2020)

3D Artist, Intern

I have previous experience as a 3D generalist at salvation games studios. My whole work dealt with delivering complete models (3D modelling plus 3D texturing) before deadline. And sometimes I was also asked to create environments with given assets or props.

Xplorazzi Adventures Pvt.Ltd (Oct 2021-April 2022)

3D Artist, Intern

I am responsible to deliver complete lowpoly 3D models for AR based application. All the models that I create is optimized to its maximum capacity, and ready to be use on any web-based platform as well.

Wow Labz (April 2022 -present)

3D Artist(fulltime)

In my present company I am working on Unity Engine to design lots of environments/ props for games, VR, metaverses. I collaborate with my fellow designers and unity developers to provide the best design visuals possible.

### Education

The Future Foundation School Mar 2017 - Mar 2019

Bhawanipore Education Society college (B.com Hons) July 2020- Present